他跑不远
He won't get far.
救命
Help.
你还醒着吗
You still awake?
高速追击途中
In the middle of a high speed chase.
最好是重要的事
This better be important.
知道你在外保证我们安全 我就感觉很好
I just feel so good knowing you're out there keeping us safe.
你那边怎么样
And yours on your end?
州警那说了一堆话
There's a mess of chatter from state police, but it
但听上去好像控制住了
sounds like they got it under control.
总之 你该起身了 这样你回来时 我们就能看到你
Anyway, you're about up so we'll see you when you get in.
好的
Okay.
等下
Hold on.
我好像看到个..
Looks like I got some kind of a...
喝醉的少年
Drunk teenager.
说不准
I don't know.
嘿
Hey!
嘿 伙计 一路爬回家
Hey, buddy, you know it's a little cold to be
有点冷啊
crawling all the way home.
等着
Stand by.
闹腾的一晚 是吧
Big night, huh?
真见鬼
Holy shit.
调度 我要送这家伙去哪
Dispatch, where am i taking this guy?
最近的急救机构仍是马什县医院
Closest emergency services is still marsh county.
那里火灾后 不知道还剩什么
Not sure what's left of it after the fire.
我以为要搬走了 但还在当班名单里
I think they're moving, but they're still listed on duty.
好吧 莱克兰呢
Okay, uh, how about lakeland?
至少还要20分钟
It's another twenty minutes atleast.
你决定吧
It's your call.
好吧 你先打个电话 说我在带他过去
Okay, you call ahead to marsh.Let them know it's me that's bringing him in.
你先打电话
You call ahead.
马什县纪念医院
有谁能帮忙吗
Can I get some help here?
贝弗 前台需要帮忙
Uh, bev, I need hands up front.
带担架来
Bring a stretcher.
调度没预先打电话来?
Dispatch not call ahead?
什么
What?
没电话啊
We didn't get a call.
贝弗
Bev!
你来抬他的脚吧
Uh, wanna get his feet?
好的 我来
Yup, I'll get him.
- 好了 一 二 三  - 一 二 三
- Okay. One, two, three. - One, two, three.
好了
Alright.
你还好吧
Are you okay?
能听到我说话吗
Can you hear me?
他怎么了 丹尼
What's his story, Danny?
他在流血 贝弗
Uh, he's bleeding, bev.
我们会照料你
We're gonna take care of you.
贝弗莉 给他上监护器 叫鲍威尔医生来
Beverly, we gotta get him on a monitor and into Dr. Powell.
走吧
Let's go.
嗨
Hi.
播送因技术问题中断后已恢复
Coming back on the air after an interruption due to technical problems.
那是什么情况
What's that about?
天知道
Who knows.
我在这做什么都不被允许
They won't let me do anything around here.
这个不错
Oh, here's a good one.
去颏套
De-gloving.
这有张图
There's a picture.
天呐
Ugh, Jesus.
统计学上来讲 相比其他地方
You know, statistically, you're more likely to die
你更可能死在医院
in a hospital than anywhere else.
太好了
Cool.
我能给你根导管
Well, I could give you a catheter.
会挺有意思
That could be fun.
你是护士吗
Are you even a nurse?
我在接受培训
I am in training.
太好了
That's so cool.
我要睡觉了 好吗
How about I'm just gonna go to sleep, okay?
反正我要走了
I should go anyway.
我想你不需要这东西了
I guess you won't be needing this.
晚安
Goodnight.
你挺会隆重登场啊 小丹尼
well, you sure know how to make an entrance, Danny boy.
是啊
Yup.
感觉怎么样 玛吉
How you feeling, Maggie?
我一直有些疼
I've been having some pains.
鲍威尔医生说孩子可能要出生了
Dr. Powell says the baby might be on it's way.
没错 她肯定在里面猛踢
Yup, she's kicking up a storm in there that's for sure.
总之
Anyhow.
我很高兴医生还在
I'm just glad the doc stuck around.
那场火灾对这地方造成了很大损失
That fire really did a number on this place.
每次那孩子一躁动
And I can't afford to be driving her into the city
就开她去城里 我可吃不消
every time that kid gets fidgety.
消停会儿吧 爷爷
Give it a rest, grandad.
放开我
Let go of me!
- 住手  - 冷静
- Stop! - Calm down.
冷静
Calm down.
- 马上好  - 放开我
- One more second. - Let go of me!
- 住手  - 马上就好
- Stop! - Just one more second.
放松 呼吸
Easy. Breathe.
好了
Okay.
这场面我可不会记着
I'm not gonna miss this.
你能搞定他吧 理查德
You gonna be able to handle him, Richard?
你这朋友遭受了不小的创伤
Your friend here's had quite a trauma.
我们没身份辨识手环了
Well, not that we have any ID bracelets left, but for
但证件表明他叫詹姆斯
the record his name is James.
他有多糟
How bad is he?
他很不配合
Well, he's not been very cooperative.
镇定剂有助于我们查明
The sedative will help us determine exactly what his
他到底是什么状况 但我们这里的资源有限
condition is, but our resources are limited here.
所有东西都被打包准备搬走了
Everything's been packed up for the move.
看来这个詹姆斯对针头并不陌生
Looks like James here isn't any stranger to needles.
你在哪发现这家伙的
Where'd you find this guy?
他的血他妈流到我身上了
He fucking bled on me.
金 我知道被转来
Kim, I know getting transferred over here
不是你的首选 但你该
wasn't your first choice, but you're supposed to be
把文件装箱
boxing up files.
不用 现在有种东西叫电脑
No, there are things called computers now.
电脑能把文件放进箱子?
Can computers put files in boxes?
谢谢你咯
Thank you!
真老派
So old school.
要去除血渍
You might need something a little stronger
你就得用更强效点的
if you're gonna get that stain out.
无所谓了 该死的
Whatever, fuck.
我能用洗衣机洗
I can do my own laundry.
瞧你那样
Well! Look at you.
我给你带了咖啡
Brought you uh, coffee.
太好了
Nice.
我之前想要来着
I was looking for that.
它现在是我的 所以别有任何想法
It's mine now so don't you get any ideas.
是啊
Right.
你真好
You're being friendly.
见到你 我很高兴
It's good to see you.
不好意思
Uh... I'm sorry.
我打断你们了吗
Am I interrupting something?
- 没有  - 没有
- No, no. - No. No, no, no.
我正想去确认下贝弗没杀掉我的实习生
I'm just gonna go make sure bev hasn't murdered my intern.τгаηslаτed ьγ ωeiьо-Eмτee
回见
I'll see you.
我们的来客暂时昏迷着
Our guest is out for now.
他伤得不严重 但你要过一段时间
He's not badly hurt, but it will be a while before
才能和他谈话
you can talk to him.
该死
Fuck.
你应该温柔对待艾莉森
You should be gentle with Alison.
她还要面对所遭遇的事
She's still coming to terms with what happened.
没错 好的
Yeah, okay.
丹尼尔 你知道没什么比
As you know Daniel, there's nothing worse than
失去孩子更糟
losing a child.
失去莎拉那会儿 我一团糟
When we lost Sarah, i was a mess.
很久才重新振作
It took a long time to come back from that.
你一定要往前看
You just have to keep going.
没错
Yeah.
贝弗莉
Beverly.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
贝弗莉
Beverly.
怎么了
What?
天啊
Jesus Christ.
你他妈在干什么 贝弗
What the fuck are you doing, bev?
贝弗利
Beverly?
这不是我的脸
This isn't my face.
什么 贝弗
What, bev?
别那么做
No, no, don't do that.
贝弗
Bev!
放下剪刀
Put the scissors down.
看着我
Look at me!
贝弗 好了 住手
Bev, okay, stop!
这不是我
It's not me.
别那么做
No, no, no, don't do that.
贝弗
Bev.
你能帮帮我吗
Can you help me?
贝弗 贝弗 别动
Bev, bev, stop!
别
No, no, no!
贝弗 别动
Beverly, stop!
该死
Oh, fuck.
丹尼尔
Daniel!
丹尼尔 怎么了
Daniel, what?
- 你做了什么 - 这他妈什么情况
- What did you do? - What the fuck?
金 金 离开这里
Kim. Kim, get out of here.
金 你不必看这个
Kim, you don't need to see this.
她杀了他 我..
She killed him. I, uh...
她要攻击我
She came at me.
她要攻击我 好了
She came at me. Okay.
好了
Alright.
是枪声吗
Was that a gunshot?
天呐 出了什么事
My god, what happened?
贝弗莉 她攻击了丹尼尔和罗宾逊的孩子
Beverly, she attacked Daniel and the Robinson kid.
好了 我得上报这件事 我得...
Okay, I gotta call this in. I gotta call- -
- 冷静下 好吗 冷静 - 我得上报
- Give yourself a second, okay?Just calm, calm down. - Tell them. I gotta...
- 让我冷静下  - 你能从
- Just give me a second. - Can you just call
- 办公室打吗 - 让我冷静下
- from the office? - Give me a second.
你感觉怎么样
How are you feeling?
什么
What?
我挺好
I'm fine.
嘘
Shh.
我没事
I'm okay.
放松 丹尼尔
Take it easy, Daniel.
看来你可能癫痫了
It looks like you might have had a seizure.
没有
No, no, no, no.
丹尼尔 你要是觉得头晕 就不该站起来
If you're feeling dizzy, Daniel, you shouldn't try to get up.
好了
Okay.
坐下 好吗
Just sit down, okay?
来
Come on.
我得上报
I gotta call it in.
你得放松下
No, you need to take it easy.
已经有一名州警到这了
There's a state trooper already here.
什么
What?
天呐 我昏迷多久了
Oh god, how long was I out for?
不久 显然他早就上路了
Not long.Apparently, he was already on his way.
跟你带来的那孩子有关 听着 现在不重要了
Something to do with that kid you brought in.Look, it's not important right now.
这州警大概会想和你谈谈
This trooper's probably gonna wanna talk to you.
我们应该考虑把你转进病房
We should see about moving you to a room.
不用
No, no, no.
你刚经历了一件极度创伤性事件
You just experienced an extremely traumatic event.
行了
Okay.
好了 听着
Okay, look.
你现在就像你父亲那样固执
You are stubborn like your father was now.
你该认真对待这问题
You should take this very seriously.
我是很固执
I- i am, I am.
我没事
I'm good.
好吧
Alright.
丹尼尔
Daniel.
米切尔
Mitchell.
你在这啊
There you are.
出什么事了
So what happened?
听说他俩是一起被你发现的
They told me you found the two of them together.
没错
Uh, yeah.
我到时 他已经死了 然后她用剪刀
He was dead when I arrived and she came at me with a
向我攻击
pair of scissors.
你到这怎么这么快
How did you get here so fast?
你那个在隔壁病房的人
Your guy in the other room.
他怎么了
What about him?
这里以北约20英里 有场大血洗
We got a major bloodbath about twenty miles north of here.
他把那地方当成屠宰店大杀特杀
Looks like he tore the place up like a butcher shop.
是的
Uh, yeah.
我们检查了他 他身上大部分血
We looked him over and most of the blood on his
不是他的
body was not his.
他有很多吸毒前科
Well he has a long list of drug related priors.
你们护士应该已有所发现
So I think he gave your nurse something.
我暂时把他铐在了床上
I've got him cuffed to the bed for the time being.
他已经失去知觉了
He's been out cold.
现在我来了
Well I'm here now.
我会处理
I'll sort it out.
我需要你的枪
I need to take your firearm.
好的
Yeah.
卡特 你爸是个可靠的警察
You know, Carter, your dad was a stand up cop.
我好奇他看到这出闹剧会怎么想
I wonder what he'd think if he saw this shit show.
好了 我们得统计所有人
Okay, we need to make sure everybody's accounted for.
这里还有谁
Who else is here?
鲍威尔医生和金
Dr. Powell and Kim.
还有本和玛吉
Oh, and um, Ben and Maggie.
她怀孕了
She's pregnant.
天呐 真麻烦
Christ, what a mess.
嘿 你介意我上报吗
Hey, uh, do you mind if I call it in?
不介意
Alright.
谢谢
Thanks.
里面打不通
I'm not getting through in here.
你收到没 米切尔
Are you copying, Mitchell?
我去车上试试
I'm gonna try the car.
收到
Copy.
调度 我是卡特 在马什县
Dispatch, this is Carter at marsh county.
收到没
Do you copy?
调度 我是卡特 在马什县
Dispatch, this is Carter at marsh county.
收到没 我有紧急情况 我需要协助
Do you copy?I have a code three and I need assist.
该死
Fuck!
嗨
Hi!
你他妈在干嘛
What the fuck are you doing?
见鬼
Shit, shit!
救命
Help me!
丹尼尔 丹尼尔 丹尼尔
Daniel, Daniel, Daniel!
理查德
Richard!
他流了很多血
He's losing a lot of blood.
按住伤口
Keep pressure over the wound.
丹尼尔 没事的 看着我
Daniel, it's fine. Look at me.
金 给我拿医药包和8毫克吗啡
Kim, I need you to bring me a sutra kit and 8mg of morphine.
睁开眼睛 看着我 听见没
Keep your eyes on me, you hear me?
你有没听到我说的
Did you hear what I said?
金 你在干嘛
Kim, what are you doing?
金 听到我说的没
Kim, did you hear me?
天呐 过来
For fuck's sake, come here.
你会没事的 丹尼尔 你会没事的
You'll be alright, Daniel, you'll be alright.
- 保持呼吸 - 双手放在这里 用力按住
- Keep breathing. - Put both your hands here. Firm pressure.
- 好的  - 别收手
- Okay. - Don't stop.
让他醒着 看着他
You keep him awake.Keep your eyes on him.
- 也让他看着你  - 好样的 丹尼尔
- Keep his eyes on you. - Good boy, Daniel.
- 好样的  - 金
- Good boy. - Kim!
别让他合眼
Don't let him close his eyes.
- 嘿 你得醒着  - 你得醒着 丹尼尔 醒着
- Hey! Stay awake. - Stay awake, Daniel, stay awake.
嘿
Hey!
丹尼尔
Daniel.
Daniel?
我暂时止住出血了
I've stopped the bleeding for now.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank god.
我们知道
We know.
嘿
Hey.
好吧 最好别站起来
Okay, maybe don't try to get up just yet.
外面出了什么事
What happened out there?
让他缓缓
Just give him a second.
看来他们包围了这地方
It looks like they've got the place surrounded.
他们并不想进来
They're not trying to get in.
他们是什么人
Who are they?
不知道
I don't know.
我打不通电话 你呢
I wasn't able to get through. You?
打不通
No.
我们该把所有人转移到后面
We should move everyone back inside.
谁知道他们想要什么
Who knows what they want.
不用 也许我们能给门设障
No, maybe we can barricade the doors or uh, you know,
或想其他办法离开
get out some other way.
见鬼 我把他忘了
Shit.I forgot about him.
做点什么啊
Do something!
开枪打它啊
Fucking shoot it!
天呐 求你了
Oh my god, please!
做点什么啊
Do something!
救我
Help me!
天呐 快他妈救我 该死的
Oh my god, fucking help me, god damnit!
救我 救我
Help me, help me!
那是什么
What is that?
我想那是贝弗莉
I think that was Beverly.
- 天呐 那是什么情况 - 我们要走了 就现在 快
- Jesus, what the hell was that? - We're leaving. Now, now, now, now.
嘿 这不是个好主意 丹尼尔
Hey, that's not a good idea, Daniel.
等下
Wait, wait, wait.
外面那些该死的疯子怎么办
What about those fucking lunatics out there?
相信我 我们还要担心其他东西
We got other things to worry about, believe me.
米切尔 米切尔 你和我 去取车 好吗
Mitchell, Mitchell!You and I, let's go get the cars, okay?
听明白没
Are you with me?
那他妈是什么情况
What the hell was that?
注意安全 退后
Make safe, back up.
离门远点
Stay away from the doors!
- 他有枪  - 退后
- He's got a gun. - Back, back, back.
好了 注意安全
Okay, make safe.
注意安全
Make safe.
好了 放下武器
Okay, okay, drop it!
Okay, drop it! Drop it!
去你妈的
Fuck you.
给我退后
Get the fuck back.
放下武器
Okay, put it down.
保持冷静
Stay calm, stay calm.
所有人都保持冷静
Whoa, everybody, just stay calm!
离我远点
Stay the fuck away from me.
冷静
Calm down!
好了 放下枪 没事的
Okay! Put down the gun,it's okay.
所有人都冷静
Everybody just calm down.
- 你说冷静? - 理查德 理查德 理查德
- Calm down, you said? - Richard, Richard, Richard.
别
No, no, no.
没必要把她牵扯进来
There's no reason to involve her in this.
- 理查德 - 这样对你毫无帮助
- Richard. - It's not gonna help you.
听着
Listen.
把刀给我就没事了
Just give me the knife and this will all be over.
这样对你毫无帮助
It isn't gonna help you.
理查德 我不知道该他妈怎么办
Richard, I don't know what to fucking do!
别担心 玛吉
Don't worry, Maggie.
他不会伤害你
He's not going to hurt you.
把刀给我吧
Just let me have it.
- 不  - 理查德
- No! - Richard!
金
Kim, Kim!
我扶着他了
I got him, I got him.
金
Kim.
看着我 看着我
Look at me, look at me.
我们不会死在这该死的地方
We are not gonna die in this fucking place!
相信我 没人想继续待在这
Nobody wants to be in here any longer than we have to.Believe me.
他哪都别想去
No, he's not going anywhere.
该死的白痴
Fucking idiot!
好了
Alright.
那他妈是什么
What the fuck was that?
亲爱的 你会没事的
Sweetheart, you're gonna be fine.
你会没事的
You're gonna be fine.
天呐 他好臭
Fuck's sake, he stinks.
米切尔
Mitchell!
退后
Stay back!
该死
Oh, fuck.
进办公室 快进办公室
Get in the office. Get in the office now.
快
Now, now!
进办公室
Get in the office.
好了 去办公室
Okay, go to the office!
那他妈是什么
What the fuck was that?
我不想和你争论 快走
I'm not gonna argue with you. Go, go!
你得告诉我那里面是什么
You need to tell me what's in there.
我不知道那里面是什么
I don't know what's in there.
- 求你快走吧  - 把门锁上
- But please, just go. - Lock the door.
好吧 等下
Okay. You hold on.
- 你们是谁 - 离我他妈的远点
- Who are you? - Get the fuck away from me.
别激动
Whoa, whoa, just slow down.
你们是谁
Who are you? Who are you?
告诉我们这个就好
Just tell us that.
我要他
I want him.
好吧 听着
Okay, look.
- 好吗 - 好的
- Alright? - Alright.
我想我们都赞同我们得离开这栋楼 对吗
I think we all agreed that we need to get the hell out of this building, right?
这些个人恩怨..
These personal differences, they're- -
丹尼尔
oh, Daniel!
住手
Stop.
谁都别想走
No one is going anywhere.
好了
Okay, alright.
好吧
Okay.
我们对这地方一无所知
We don't know anything about this place.
你让我们来这 我们就不能相信他们
If you let us here, we can't trust them.
你不必这么做
You don't need to do this.
住手
Stop!
他没法回应你
He can't answer you.
肖恩
Shaun!
看见没
See?
那是他最后信任的一个人干的
That's what the last people he trusted did.
你错了 你们能相信我们
No, you're making a mistake. You can trust us, you can trust us.
我可不这么认为
I don't think so.
等下 别这样
Wait, wait!Please, please!
把你的手拿开
Get your hands off me.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
冷静
You calm down.
好了 和谐
Okay, we're good.
你想再次经历这一切?
You wanna go through all this again?
我知道你相信我跟你说我们不知道
I know you believe me when i tell you we don't know
这他妈是什么情况
what the fuck is going on, okay?
我...
I...
她体内有东西长出来
There were things growing out of her.
你看见了 你也是
You saw it, you saw it.
那是什么
What was that?
我们能把这地方剩下的烧了
We could uh, burn what's left of the place.
这样干光他们
Take them all with it.
好了 听我说
Okay, listen to me.
我们对你没做过任何事
We didn't do anything to you.
里面有个临产的姑娘
I have a girl back there who's about to give birth
我得带她去安全处
and I need to get her some place safe.
你他妈在逗我吗
Are you fucking kidding?
你看过外面吗 女士
Have you had a look outside lady?
无处可走
There's nowhere to go.
你能在数英里外听到那些号角声
You can hear those horns for miles.
有东西在把他们召唤过来
There is something calling them all here.
好吧 那是什么 他们是谁...
Okay, what is that? Who are they? What just- -
我他妈怎么知道
how the fuck should I know?
- 去问他们  - 好吧 好吧
- Go ask them! - It's okay, it's okay.
我只知道那东西已经醒过一次了
All I know is that that thing woke up once already
我不希望再有这种事发生
and I don't wanna be around when it happens again.
有个问题
Oh, there's a problem.
玛吉
Maggie.
我不知道该做什么
I didn't know what to do.
好吧
Okay.
嘿 亲爱的
Hey, sweetie.
我们要走了吗
Are we leaving?
还不是现在
No, not just yet.
你能把那东西灭掉吗
Would you put that out?
艾莉
Al.
- 什么 这个? - 是啊
- What, this? - Yeah.
把它灭了
Put it out.
好了 我想大家都该保持冷静
Okay.I think we all should just remain calm.
放屁
Bullshit.
我们本该离开这里
We should've been out of here already.
你们这些人得醒醒了
You people need to wake up.
不然呢
Or what?
外面要是有另一个那样的东西
You think you'll stand a chance if there's another
你们觉得你们跑得掉?
one of those things out there?
- 好吧 - 跑得掉吗
- Okay. - Will you, huh?
- 好吧  - 谁能阻止它 爷爷?
- Okay, okay. - Who's gonna stop it? Grandpa?
十几岁的浪货?
The teenage fucking slut?
来啊
Oh! Come on now!
别这样
Come on.
我们会死的
We're gonna die.
不会 我们不会死
No, we're not gonna die.
你们会死
You're gonna die.
我不会让这种事发生
I'm not gonna let that happen.
好吧
Okay.
我不知道你他妈想干嘛
I don't know what the fuck you think you're trying to do.
- 冷静 好吗 - 他在扰乱她 这可不好
- Okay? Just calm down. - He's upsetting her and that is not good.
- 我要你保持冷静  - 好的
- I need you to stay calm. - Okay.
能告诉我那边什么情况吗
Can you please tell me what is going on over there?
她还在宫缩
Her contractions are still spread out, but she's
但她腹痛 这不是好征兆
having abdominal pain which is a bad sign.
好吧 我不懂这是什么意思
Okay, I don't know what that means.
- 这是什么意思 - 意思是我们不能转移她
- What does that mean? - That means that we can't move her.
那会让情况恶化
It can make things much worse.
此外 在这过程中
Also the last thing I need is to be performing a
我要施行剖腹产 但这里没我
cesarean in the middle of this, but I have nothing
能用来帮她的 我什么都不做 孩子就会死
here to help her and if I don't do anything the baby could die.
我得去药房
I need to go to the med supply room.
我要去
So I'll go.
一个人? 不行 不可能
Alone? No, no, no, that's out of the question.
我可不是在请求
I'm not asking.
我们现在得处理这事
We need to handle this now.
好吧
Alright.
好了 听着 我们不知道外面有什么
Okay, look.We have no idea what is out there.
我们没法保护自己
We have no way of defending ourselves.
另外  现在有两个疯子
Plus these two fucking psychos now think that
把我们当人质
we're hostage.
我要去
I'm doing this.
不行...
You're not. You're not. You're not even...
如果这是因为我们的孩子 那你得做个
If this is because of the baby then you need to get
该死的心理检查
a fucking mental check.
天呐 这和我们的事无关
Jesus Christ, this is not about us.
那姑娘 她要是遭受胎盘早剥
That girl, if she suffers an abruption
她的孩子就会死
then her baby will die.
把孩子弄出来 我不用
If I try to take it out of her, and I don't use
麻醉剂 她就会休克而死
anesthetic then she could die of shock.
丹尼尔 看着我
Daniel, look at me.
好吧 该死的
Okay, fine. Fuck it, fuck it.
好吧 但你不能一个人去
Okay, but you're not going alone.
你得保证 然后等我 好吗 你保证?
You have to promise and wait for me, okay? You promise?
- 保证 - 好的
- Okay. - Alright.
我能提议吗
May I approach?
那姑娘的情况不乐观 孩子也是
The girl's not doing well and neither is the baby so
我们得去弄些东西来帮她
we need to go and get some things to help her.
你想要我们干嘛
What do you want from us?
我的巡逻车里有霰弹枪
Well I have a shotgun in my cruiser.
还有弹药
I have ammunition.
我们刚一路血战进来
We just fought our way in here.
我不会再出去
I'm not gonna just stroll back out again.
好吧 在我看来 我们的处境都一样
Okay, but as far as I can tell we're all the same boat.
你的步枪没子弹了
You've got a rifle without any bullets and a couple
还两把该死的消防斧
of fucking fire axes.
车很近 我们的动作能迅速点
I just...It's close and we can do it fast.
好吧 但我们不是为你们冒生命危险
Alright, but we're not risking our lives for you.
我们拿到枪 枪就是我们的
We get that gun, it's ours.
绝对是
Oh, absolutley.
绝对他妈是
Abso-fucking-lutley.
好
Okay.
你说很近的
I thought you said it was close.
什么情况
What the hell?
还在外面
It's still out there.
是的 但他们在等什么
Yeah, but what are they waiting for?
我们速去速回
Let's just make this quick.
霰弹枪被锁在前座
Shotgun's locked on the front seat.
我得开锁 不过...
I gotta release it, but...
弹药在后备箱
You get all the ammo out of the trunk.
别耍小聪明
Don't get any bright ideas.
嘿 等下
Hey, hold up.
该死的
God damnit.
他们回不来怎么办
What if they don't come back?
丹尼尔有数的
Daniel knows what he's doing.
没事的
It's alright.
我现在根本不该在这里
I shouldn't even be here right now.
我应该在莱克兰给病人翻身
I should be at lakeland turning over patients.
这地方真该死
Fuck this place.
金 你现在和我们困在一起 所以面对现实吧
Well, you're stuck with us now, Kim, so deal with it.
你怎么样了 亲爱的
How you doing, honey?
很疼
It hurts.
我的孩子会怎么样
What's gonna happen to my baby?
听我说
Listen to me.
你和你的孩子不会有事
You and your baby are going to be fine.
我向你保证
You have my word.
见鬼
Shit.
该死
Fuck.
你他妈搞什么呢
What the fuck are you doing in there?
你他妈怎么回事
What the fuck's going on in there?
见鬼
Ah, shit.
好了 时间到了
K, time's up.
我们该走了
That's our cue to leave.
快点 该死的
Come on, god damnit!
天呐
Fuck's sake!
快点
Fucking hurry up!
小心
Look out!
枪我拿
I'm keeping the fucking gun.
这地方挡不住任何进犯
This place isn't gonna keep anything out.
天啊
Oh my god.
嘿
Hey.
该死
Fuck.
出什么事了
What happened?
给
Here, here.
- 艾莉呢 - 她去给玛吉拿药了
- Where's Allie? - Well she went to get some medicine for Maggie.
哪
Where?
药房
The med room.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
她说这里面没什么好担心的
She said there wasn't anything to worry about inside.
你们在不在同一栋楼里啊
Are you guys in the same fucking building?
你能在这里看好他们吗
Would you please wait here, look after them?
先生 不好意思 你能跟我走吗
Excuse me, sir, would you mind following me?
谢谢了
Thank you.
那孩子不会有事
That kid will be fine.
他经历过更糟的事
He's been through a lot worse.
那些人杀了他的家人
Those people killed his family.
我勉强才把他救了出来
I barely got him out of there alive.
你是什么来头 神秘男子
Yeah, what about you, man of mystery?
管好你自己的事
Mind your own business.
对了 她一个人走开太傻了
And by the way, pretty stupid to go running off by herself.
好吧 我非常肯定你能揍扁我
Okay, I'm pretty certain you can beat the shit out
但我认为我才是有权
of me, but I consider it my special privilege to
责备我妻子的人 所以请你给我闭嘴
hate my wife right now so if you could kindly shut the fuck up.
这是米切尔的枪
This is Mitchell's gun.
看
Look.
怎么了
What?
你好 丹尼尔
Hello, Daniel.
这是谁
Who is this?
你看到了...
You saw...
一些东西
Something.
你醒来时 我就感觉到了
I felt it when you woke up.
但那是什么呢
But what was it?
你愿意的话 我能向你展现更多
I can show you more if you'd like.
嗨 理查德
Hi, Richard.
我肯定这对你来说很难理解
I'm sure it's hard for you to understand.
贝弗莉也是 但我向你保证
Beverly found it difficult as well, but I assure you
我的目的有利于他人
my intentions are altruistic.
请告诉我你做了什么
Please tell me what you've done.
理查德
Richard.
理查德 告诉我
Richard, tell me.
告诉我
Tell me!
你如此努力地追随你父亲的
You're trying so hard to follow in your father's
脚步 丹尼尔
footsteps, Daniel.
你真想追随他到他的所去之处吗
Do you really wanna follow him where he's gone?
我理解失去会让你多么绝望
I understand how desperate loss can make you.
你带艾莉森来我这的那晚
The night you brought Allison to me, the life
她体内的生命拼命地要出来
inside her desperately clawing to get out.
失去女儿改变了我 但我在做
Losing my daughter changed me, but I'm doing what I
必须做的 来纠正
have to to make it right.
你很快就会明白
You'll understand soon enough.
请告诉我艾莉森在哪
Just please, can you please tell me where Allison is?
就…
Just...
你告诉我 该死的
You tell me, god damnit.
告诉我她在哪
You tell me where she is.
别担心 丹尼尔
Don't worry, Daniel.
我会帮助她
I'm gonna help her.
我会帮助你们所有人
I'm gonna help all of you.
这太疯狂了 我不知道我在做什么
This is crazy! I don't know what I'm doing.
你不能就这么离开我们
You can't just leave us.
金 我们别无选择 艾莉森是唯一知道怎么照顾玛吉的人
Kim, Kim, Kim. We don't have a choice.Allison's the only one who knows how to look after Maggie.
拜托了 听着
Please, look.
就…
Just...
这东西在里面似乎还能通信
These still seem to work inside.
不要
No.
我们保持联系 以防万一
We'll keep in touch just in case.
我们不会离开很久 不会走远
We're not gonna be gone long, we're not going far.
- 听着  - 好疼
- Look. - It hurts.
我好疼
It hurts so bad.
我不知道这是什么东西
I don't know what half this stuff is!
求你别走
Please, please don't- -
请听我说  我们只是到下面去 我们会
Listen to me, please.We're just gonna down there, I'm gonna bring
带回艾莉森 我要你坚守到那时候 好吗
back Allison, and I need you to hold out until then, alright?
如果出了什么事呢 如果那些人进来呢
What if something happens? What if those people get in here?
那我们该怎么办
What are we supposed to do?
那些人不会进来
Those people are not trying to get in here.
那些人是不想我们出去
Those people are trying to keep us from getting out.
好了 我只能做这么多了
Okay, that's the best that I can do.
但愿你知道怎么用
I hope you know how to use it.
还有...
And uh...
这个用来以防万一
That's there just in case.
你最好知道你在做什么
You better know what you're doing.
- 好了 走吧 - 你以为下去就好了?
- Okay, let's go. - You think were just gonna go down there and that'll be that?
你有话就说啊 自以为是的混蛋
If you have something to say than say it, you smug fuck.
你知道下面有什么吗
Do you know what's down there?
不知道
Nope.
但我知道谁或许知道
But I know someone who might.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 冰毒男孩
Hey, meth boy.
见鬼
Oh shit.
太好了 你还记得我们
Oh, good, you remember us.
这不是我的错 好吗
It's not my fault, okay?
你们必须相信我
You gotta believe me.
我他妈什么都没干
I didn't fucking do anything.
- 省省吧  - 请帮帮我
- Just save it. Save it! - Please help me!
- 这些家伙会杀了我  - 嘿
- These guys are gonna kill me! - Hey!
你要注意听我的问题
You're gonna wanna pay attention to my questions.
别这样 等下
Please. No, wait, wait, wait!
天呐 别这样
Oh god, please don't!
- 好吧 选根手指  - 别这样
- Alright, pick a finger. - Don't do this.
不要 你还没提问啊
No, no, you didn't ask me anything yet!
我想让你知道我是动真格的
I wanna make sure you know I'm serious.
- 我信 - 好了 嘿
- I fucking believe you. - Okay, okay, hey!
你知道什么能对我们的安全有帮助吗
Do you know anything that will help keep us safe?
什么都行 能帮我们活下来的
Anything at all?Anything that will help us survive.
跟那个该死的医生有关
It's the fucking doctor.
It's that fucking doctor.
好了 我们已经知道了
Okay, fine, we know that already.
我们没时间了
We don't have time for this.
好了 你知道吗
Alright, you know what?
- 下手麻利点 - 别这样 跟他有关
- Make it clean. - No, no, please. It is him.
跟他有关 我杀了他  我发誓我帮了你们个大忙
It's him and I killed him.I swear to god I did you a fucking favor.
是啊 他死不了
Yeah, well he's not dead anymore.
怎么会这样
How is that possible?
什么
What?
天啊
Oh god.
不要
Oh, no, no!
看着我
Look at me, look at me!
天啊
Oh god!
闭嘴
Stop!
听我说
Listen to me.
他怎么会活着 他是什么
How is he alive? What is he?
我他妈不知道啊
I don't fucking know.
好了 砍掉他的手
Okay, take his hand off.
不要 求你了
No, no, please, please!
我真的不知道
I don't know, I'm serious.
我在路上遇到个女孩
I met a girl on the road.
别动手 我在路上遇到个女孩 她跟我说
Fucking please, please, please.I met a girl on the road and she told me she could
她能帮我搞到冰毒 所以我跟她去了那个毒品屋
help me score crystal so i followed her to this fucking pill house.
其实那不是毒品屋
Except it wasn't a pill house.
是什么
What was it?
是个在荒郊野外的老农房
It was an old farm house in the middle of nowhere.
全是这些该死的吸毒者
All of these fucking junkies.
那里一塌糊涂 他们似乎杀人杀了有一阵子了
It was a mess.It looked like they'd been killing people for a while.
他提供我们毒品
He gave us drugs.
他看我们做爱
He watched us have sex.
- 他管那地方叫教堂 - 好了 你意思是 理查德
- And he called the place a church. - Okay, what you're telling me that Richard was some
是个性魔教主?
kind of sex fiend, religious thing?
我爸认识他好多年了 我们都是
My dad knew him for years, we all did.
简直胡扯
That's bullshit.
他们就穿成这样
They were dressed just like this.
有一堆人穿成这样 好吗
There's a bunch of people dressed like this, okay?
他们杀人 献祭
And they did killings and sacrifices
还让我们看
and they made us watch.
你说的是恶魔崇拜?
You're talking devil worshiping?
不是
No.
我不相信恶魔
No, I don't believe in the devil.
但我相信这个
Okay, but i believe in this.
他们能改变人
They made people change.
我看见了
I saw it.
谢谢
Thank you.
你跟我们一起去
You're coming with us.
没必要谢我们
There's no reason to thank us.
什么
What?
没错 你知道吗 我们要去地下室拜访你朋友
Yeah.You know what? We're gonna visit your friend in the basement.
不要
No!
你们疯了吗
Are you nuts?
不要 你们看到他能做什么了
No, you've seen he can do.
我们离开这里 好吗
Let's just get out of here, okay?
让这地方见鬼去吧
Fuck this place.
是吗 看下吧
Yeah? Have a look.
看吧
Go on.
请便吧
Be my guest.
不要 这是自杀
No, this is suicide.
天呐 不要 你们和他们一样疯狂
Oh my god.No, you're as crazy as they are.
或许吧
Yeah, maybe.
危险 此区域投入使用并不安全 请勿进入
这边
Down here.
譯禇 覹愽 Emtёё
这里像是会塌了似的
Looks like this place is gonna collapse.
能听到我讲话吗
Can you hear me okay?
很清楚
Loud and clear.
去地下室的楼梯井在大楼后方
The stairwell to the basement is at the back of the building.
收到
Roger that.
我知道了
Got it.
瞧
Look.
有人在这待过
Someone's been here.
金
Kim!
- 怎么走 - 停尸间的门应该就在你们前方
- Where are we going? - The door to the morgue should be right there in front of you.
我没看到门 只有过道
I don't see any door. Just a bunch of corridors.
你确定这地方没错?
You sure this is the right place?
他走错楼梯了
He went down the wrong stairs.
只有一段楼梯
There's only one set of stairs.
我知道他们要去哪
I know where they're going.
有人吗
Hello?
卡特
Carter!
最好别把我们带进陷阱
Better not be leading us into a trap.
怎么了
What's going on?
开什么玩笑
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
你找到了?
Did you find it?
是不是有下层地下室...
Is there some kind of sub-basement or...
没 你在说什么
No, no, no, what are you talking about?
- 有一段下去的楼梯  - 什么
- A staircase going down. - What?
卡特 听得到吗
Carter, can you hear me?
我们得回去
We gotta go back.
我不能叫你跟我下去
I can't ask you to follow me down here.
明白吗
You understand?
伙计们 怎么了
Guys, what's happening?
没怎么 我们...
Nothing. We're...
我们要下去
We're gonna go down the stairs.
嘿 让他带路
Hey, leading in with him.
嘿 你先走
Hey, you get to go first.
没错
Yeah, right.
这不是请求
I'm not asking.
安静
Be quiet.
别费心了
Don't bother.
你动不了
You won't be able to move.
什么 理查德?
What? Richard?
耐心点
Be patient.
我快准备好了
I'm almost ready.
什么情况
What- what- what is this?
我看见你死了
I saw you die.
我不知道那会是这种感觉
I had no idea that it would feel like this.
多年来 我给人做手术
The years I spent operating on people.
切开再缝合
Opening them up and stitching them back together again.
非常棒 那感觉...
It's remarkable, the sensation it's...
并不疼 而更是种解脱
Not pain, more a sense of release.
你为什么...
Why, why are you- -
请安静
be quiet, please.
这是个未知领域
This is uncharted territory.
是个研究自我转变的机会
The chance to study my own transformation.
我理解你的迟疑 艾莉森 但
I understand your hesitation, Allison, but
我问问你 这些年来 你有没
let me ask you, all these years, haven't you ever
想救活一个无法救活的人
wished to save someone beyond saving?
无论代价是什么
No matter what the costs?
失去莎拉 把我毁了
Well, losing Sarah destroyed me.
但也迫使我找到了解决办法
But it also compelled me to find a solution.
你有所寻求时 你会对你发现的东西感到惊叹
You'd be surprised at the things you find when you go looking.
气味像墓地
It smells like a grave.
我以前见过这场景
I've seen this place before.
是在我们清理的那栋房子里
This was all over the house we cleaned out.
他让我们看东西
He made us look at things.
那是我见过的最糟的东西
The worst things I've ever seen.
我们在那地方的地下室房间里发现全是尸体
We found rooms full of bodies in the basement of that place.
一个人被弄在桌子上 就像在被手术
They had someone on a table like they were doing surgery down there.
有一半转变成了那种东西
Half turned into one of those things.
不是
No!
比那更糟
No, worse than that.
就像一场噩梦
Like a nightmare.
这不是真的
It isn't real.
It's not real.
这是个老鼠迷宫
It's a rat's maze.
卡特
Carter!
他在这吗
Is he here?
嘿
Hey!
在啊
Yeah.
他把我带过来...孩子
He has took me here to... baby.
我就在这 孩子
I'm right here, kiddo.
会好的 没事的
It's okay, it's alright.
你会没事的
You're gonna be fine.
你很幸运 你爷爷很关心你
You're lucky your grandpa cares about you so much.
我爷爷只会对电视大吼 一直抽烟
My grandpa just yells at his TV and smokes.
- 帮帮她 - 见鬼 好的 等下
- Help her, help her. - Shit, okay, okay! Wait, wait.
请帮帮她
Help her, please.
- 可待因  - 好的
- The codeine, I think. - Alright.
好了 玛吉 坚持会儿
Okay, Maggie, hold still for one second.
有这个 好了
I got this. Okay.
这东西能
I'm gonna give you something that's really
帮到你
gonna help you.
你就不会疼了
It's gonna feel really good.
- 你表现得很棒  - 没事的
- You're doing real good. - It's alright, it's alright.
- 好了  - 不疼的
- Okay. - It's gonna be real painless.
马上就好了
It's gonna be okay in a second.
- 好的  - 马上好
- Okay, okay. - Just give me a second.
好了
Okay, okay.
好吧 你得抱她依然
Okay, you gotta hold her still.
你别让她乱动
You gotta hold her still.
我一注射 你就放松 好吗
Easy, once I get this in. Okay, ready?
打针咯
There you go.
很好
Yeah, yeah.
没事的
It's okay.
没问题的
There's no problem. No problem.
译者:微博@Emtee
很好
Great.
我不会进去的
I'm not going in there.
开枪打我吧
Fucking shoot me.
嘿
Hey.
就是这个
This is it.
就是什么
This is what?
我欣赏你的热忱 但我们得好好想想
I appreciate your enthusiasm but we need to think this through.
这是个错误
This is a mistake.
过来 小混球
Come here, you little fuck.
你知道你死后会去哪吗
Do you know where you go when you die?
我知道
I do.
你的行程会继续 会重生为别的东西
You travel on, reborn into something else, like a
就像毛毛虫变成蛾
caterpillar becoming a moth.
到现在为止 我只能追踪在虫茧里的蛾
Until now I've only been able to track the moth in its cocoon.
当然身体必须进行调整
The body has to adjust, of course.
以来适应
It adapts.
我们生来并不是这种东西
We weren't built for this kind of thing.
我承认 早期我犯了错误
I admit, early on i made mistakes.
其中有些错误还和我们在这下面
Some of those earliest mistakes are still down here with us.
事实上是他们引起了毁掉这家医院的火灾
In fact, they caused the fire that destroyed this hospital.
瞧 他们想死 但我不准
You see, they want to die, but I won't let them.
别哭泣 艾莉森
Don't cry, Allison.
我要帮助你
I am going to help you.
这是生死轮回的终结
This is an end to the cycle of life and death.
你真的想要这样的世界吗
Do you really want this world?
想要这个夺走你儿子的世界?
This world that took your son from you?
你知道那晚你未出生的孩子怎么回事吗
Do you know what happened that night to your unborn child?
别这样
No, please.
脐带缠在一起了
Umbilical cord became entangled.
就这么简单 很奇怪 对吗
Simple as that. Strange, isn't it?
你和你孩子之间的生命线
The very lifeline between you and your child,
在他挣扎着想出来时 就如套着他颈部的绞索在收紧
constricting like a noose around his neck as he struggled to get out.
越收越紧 直到他最终无法挣扎为止
Tighter and tighter until finally it couldn't struggle anymore.
大自然的无用之举
Nature's futility.
我能制止它
I can stop it.
这是真正有意义的第一步
This is the first real step.
真正意义上的复活
The true resurrection.
我失去了我女儿 她去了阴间 但今晚
I lost my daughter to the abyss, but tonight, I am
我要复活她
calling her back.
理查德
Richard.
别这样
Please.
别这么做
Don't do this.
但已经完成了
But it's already done.
你很漂亮 艾莉森
You are so beautiful, Allison.
你会变得非同凡响
You will become something truly remarkable.
这是个屠宰场
This is a slaughter house.
给我解开手铐
Get this off of me!
给我闭嘴
Shut the fuck up!
我本该在那栋房子里杀了你
I should've killed you back at the house.
冷静
Get a hold of yourself.
她还好吗
Is she alright?
她很热
She feels hot.
天啊
Oh god.
- 天呐 帮帮忙啊 - 天呐 好的
- Lord! Do something! - Oh god, okay!
好吧
Okay!
冷静
Get a hold of yourself.
去你妈的
Fuck you.
看看周围
Look around us, huh?
我跟你说了
I told you.
这是个错误
This was a mistake.
他知道些事
He knows something.
我们要你和我们在一起
We need you with us.
他在他的脑海里
He's in his head!
住手
Stop it!
我们是在地狱
We're in hell.
别让她乱动
You've got to hold her still!
不会有事的
It's gonna be okay!
是前门
That's the front entrance!
你要去哪
Where are you going?
醒醒 该死的
Wake up, damnit!
- 我做不到  - 你必须这么做
- I can't do it! - You have to!
不要
No! No! No! No! No!
做你必须做的
You do what you have to do!
我要把那些混蛋赶出去
I'll keep those bastards out.
我怕失手害死她
I can't kill her.
你必须帮她
You have to do this.
你是她唯一的机会
You are the only chance she has.
不
No.
求你了
Please!
对不起 我办不到
Sorry, I can't.
求你了
Please do this!
天呐
Oh my god!
你为什么那么做
Why did you do that?
终于是时候了
It's finally time.
你怎么能这样
How could you?
你的孩子
Your baby.
鲍威尔医生是个伟大的人
Doctor Powell is a great man.
我很幸运怀着他的孩子
I'm lucky to carry his child.
现在其他都无关紧要了
Nothing else matters now.
别担心
Don't worry.
一切都即将改变
Everything is about to change.
给我滚远点
Get the fuck away from me!
等着就好
Just wait.
我们该怎么办
What do we have to do?
等着就好
Just wait.
这是你的错
This is your fault.
This is your fault!
我当时不在
I wasn't there.
你本该保护他们
You should've protected them!
母亲要我们留下
Mother wants us to stay.
我跟你说了 照顾他们
I told you, look after them.
但你留了下来
But you stayed here.
你本该保护他们
You should have protected them!
留在这 留在这
Stay here, stay here.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这是什么情况
What is this?
卡特 卡特 卡特
Carter, Carter, Carter!
卡特 你在哪
Carter, where are you?
给我闭嘴
Shut the fuck up, shut the fuck up, shut the fuck up.
闭嘴
Shut up.
该死
Fuck!
丹尼尔
Daniel?
艾莉森
Allison.
你在哪
Where are you?
我好害怕
I'm scared.
别怕
No, no, no, no.
艾莉森 我就在这
Allison, I'm right here.
我就在这
I'm right here. I'm right here.
看着我 没事了
Look at me, it's okay.
我感觉要生了
Oh, I can feel it coming.
抓住我的手
Hold my hand.
我需要你
I need you.
我不会离开
I'm not gonna leave.
丹尼尔
Daniel.
我知道你的秘密
I know your secret.
我从你脸上看出来了
I saw it in your face.
艾莉森失去你孩子的那晚
The night Allison lost your child.
我看到了解脱
I saw relief.
你做了什么
What have you done?
我给了她想要的
I've given her what she wanted.
她是个母亲
She's a mother.
她不漂亮吗
Isn't she beautiful?
丹尼尔
Daniel.
留下来
Stay.
你看到了吗 丹尼尔
Do you see, Daniel?
告诉我你看到的
Tell me what you see.
我看到
I see...
一个自认为是神的怪物
A monster that thinks he's god.
真让我失望
I'm disappointed.
我向你展现了一切 你却仍不明白
Of all the things I've shown you and you still don't understand.
没错
No.
你说得没错 我不明白
No, you're right, I don't.
我拒绝让死亡成为终结
I refuse to let death be the end.
我违抗神
I defy god.
世上有更为古老的存在
There are things much older.
比时间还古老 他们祝福了我
Older than time and they blessed me.
恭喜
Well, congratulations.
我一生都在对抗死亡 但现在我明白了
I spent my life resisting death, but now I understand.
我必须接受它
I must embrace it.
我将复活我的美丽女儿
I'll have my beautiful daughter back.
我只需要最后一样东西
I just need one final thing.
来吧 加入我
Come, join me.
其他人都聚集于此 来见证我女儿的重生
The others have all gathered to witness my daughter's rebirth.
我的信徒们准备好转变了
My disciples ready for their own transformation.
你可以亲自体验下 但首先
You'll experience it yourself, but first,
你得为我而死...
you have to die for me...
就如你之前的父亲和儿子
Like your father and son before you.
你做得太棒了 亲爱的
You've done wonderfully, my dear.
现在看着吧
Now watch.
你将是我的观众
You will be my audience.
看着阴间向我敞开吧
Watch the abyss open itself to me.
来祝福我的孩子吧
Come and bless my baby.
把我的女儿放入这个容器
Place my daughter into this vessel.
没错
Yes.
把你自己献给她吧
Give yourself to her.
让她出来吧
Let her come to be.
这就是她
It's her.
你看到了吗
You see?
嘿
Hey!
小心
Look out!
动手
Do it!
我们都将被拯救
We will all be saved.
这由世间一切所导致
Everything has led to this.
我能看透我面前的一切
I can see it all before me.
无限运转的异界
The infinite astro workings.
好美
It's beautiful.
别反抗了 丹尼尔
Don't fight it, Daniel.
我能把艾莉森给你
I can give Allison to you.
她就是你想要的 对吗
That's what you want, isn't it?
她在等你
She's waiting for you.
你只要死 你们就能在一起了
All you have to do is let go and you can be together.
真听话
That's a good boy.
这并不是结束
This isn't the end.
是结束
Yes.
结束了
结束了吗
Is it over?